People, they like to see images that reflect concepts that are in their hearts.
Az emberek szeretik látni a képeket, melyek visszatükrözik a szívükben lévő elképzeléseket.
[Heart Movies]
[Szívben rejlő filmek]
We can see in the senses the subjective realm, and what we see, objective,
Látjuk az érzékelésekben a szubjektív birodalmat, de amit fizikálisan látunk, az objektív,
and we’re forever trying to take what’s in the heart out into the objective world.
És örökké megpróbáljuk megjeleníttetni a világban azt, ami a szívünkben van.
Actually, really we want to live in the subjective world
Valójában a szubjektív világban akarunk élni,
but we find ourselves in the objective world,
de az objektív világban találjuk magunkat,
and that’s why people— not only the Chinese, but everybody—
és ezért van az, hogy az emberek - nemcsak a kínaiak, hanem mindenki -
they like to go to movies and immerse themselves in an experience,
szeretnek moziba menni és belemeríteni magukat egy élménybe,
it’s like you’re taken away from the objective world for some time
kilépni az objektív világból egy kis időre,
and you enter another world,
és belépni egy másik világba,
and you’re voyeuristically envisioning yourself through the characters there.
és lelki szemeiddel ott látni magadat a karakteren keresztül.
That’s in a simple way; that’s part of what people do through media,
Ez egy egyszerű módja, amit az emberek a médián keresztül csinálnak,
but there may be more profound implications about that also.
de talán mélyebb összefüggések vannak még erről.